"Not Only This, But New Language Beckons Us" Exhibition Archive 2013 MSS.373
Fales Library and Special Collections
"Not Only This, But New Language Beckons Us" Exhibition Archive
2013
Fales Library and Special Collections
Blackley, Andrew
MSS.373
0.2 Linear Feet
This collection comprises original materials, and facsimiles of materials, exhibited in the show "Not Only This, But New Language Beckons Us", held at the Fales Library & Special Collections Tracey/Barry Gallery in 2013, as well as records created and compiled by the exhibition's curator, Andrew Blackley. The exhibition took place on the occasion of the 25th anniversary of Visual AIDS, a non-profit organization based in New York whose mission is to "utilize art to fight AIDS by provoking dialogue, supporting HIV+ artists, and preserving a legacy, because AIDS is not over."
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Historical Note
"Not only this, but new language beckons us" was an exhibition held in 2013 at the Fales Library & Special Collections' Tracey/Barry Gallery on the occasion of the 25th anniversary of Visual AIDS, a non-profit organization based in New York whose mission is to "utilize art to fight AIDS by provoking dialogue, supporting HIV+ artists, and preserving a legacy, because AIDS is not over." The exhibition was organized by curator Andrew Blackley, who invited artists and writers to select archival documents from the Fales Downtown Collection and to write texts to accompany their selections, which were displayed together in the gallery.
Scope and Content
This collection comprises original materials, and facsimiles of materials, exhibited in the show "Not Only This, But New Language Beckons Us", held at the Fales Library & Special Collections Tracey/Barry Gallery in 2013, as well as records created and compiled by the exhibition's curator, Andrew Blackley.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into two series. Series II is arranged alphanetically by name of contributing artist.
Provenance
The collection was donated to NYU's Fales Library & Special Collections by curator Andrew Blackley in 2013.
Artists and community -- United States; Art -- Exhibitions.; AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Downtown Collection.; Visual AIDS (Organization)
- Series I: Administrative
  Scope and Content
  Series I contains
  - Postcard, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Checklist, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series II: Artists' Texts
  - Ault, Julie: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ault, Julie: Martin Wong Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bellamy, Dodie: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bellamy, Dodie: Kathy Acker Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bordowitz, Gregg: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bordowitz, Gregg: Frank Moore Document, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brody, Nancy Brooks: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brody, Nancy Brooks: Martin Wong Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Burgher, Elijah: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Burgher, Elijah: Dennis Cooper Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Burkhart, Kathe: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Burkhart, Kathe: Cookie Mueller Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Carrillo, Sean: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Carrillo, Sean: Jack Smith Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cramer, Peter: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cramer, Peter: Stephen Kent Jusick Document, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gangitano, Lia: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gangitano, Lia: Hunter Reynolds Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Herrmann, Matthias: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Herrmann, Matthias: Wojnarowicz and Peter Hujar Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hubbard, Jim: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Hubbard, Jim: James Wentzy Media, 1994, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ischar, Doug: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ischar, Doug: Wojnarowicz Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Jones, William E.: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Jones, William E.: "Polysexuality" Documents, c. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Keene, John: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Keene, John: Martin Wong Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Killian, Kevin: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Killian, Kevin: Wojnarowicz Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Nathanael: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Nathanael: Wojnarowicz Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Neff, John: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Neff, John: John Neff/Blanchon Documents, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Parnes, Uzi: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Parnes, Uzi: Lou Maletta Document, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Patten, Mary: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Patten, Mary: Robert Blanchon Document, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sobell, Nina: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Sobell, Nina: Stuart Sherman Document, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Troyano, Ela: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Troyano, Ela: Jack Smith Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ultra-Red: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ultra-Red: Wojnarowicz Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Waters, Jack: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Waters, Jack: Jack Waters Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Westmoreland, Joe: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Westmoreland, Joe: Dennis Cooper Documents, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Vo, Danh: Text, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Vo, Danh: Martin Wong Document, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)